[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひっこしします' read in word?",
        "answer": "Переїжджати"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かよいます' read in word?",
        "answer": "Відвідувати"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'そば, がわ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Сторона, бік"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ころ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Період, час, пора"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ところで' read in word?",
        "answer": "Доречі"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ことば' read in word?",
        "answer": "слово"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せっとうじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "префікс"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せつびじ' read in word?",
        "answer": "суфікс"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'だいがっこう' read in word?",
        "answer": "велика школа"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんじてんしゃ' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий велосипед"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふしんせつ' read in word?",
        "answer": "не дружній"
    },
    {
        "id": "12",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごじゅうしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "адреса (ввічливо)"
    },
    {
        "id": "13",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんきゅうじょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "лабораторія"
    },
    {
        "id": "14",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えいがかん' read in word?",
        "answer": "кінотеатр"
    },
    {
        "id": "15",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'おんがくか' read in word?",
        "answer": "музикант"
    },
    {
        "id": "16",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どうぶつえん' read in word?",
        "answer": "зоопарк"
    },
    {
        "id": "17",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'どうぶつ' read in word?",
        "answer": "тварина"
    },
    {
        "id": "18",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'えん' read in word?",
        "answer": "парк"
    },
    {
        "id": "19",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'としょかん' read in word?",
        "answer": "бібліотека"
    },
    {
        "id": "20",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふるほんや' read in word?",
        "answer": "старий книжний"
    },
    {
        "id": "21",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんぶんしゃ' read in word?",
        "answer": "видання газет"
    },
    {
        "id": "22",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふゆうめい' read in word?",
        "answer": "не популярний"
    },
    {
        "id": "23",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ごはん' read in word?",
        "answer": "їжа, рис"
    },
    {
        "id": "24",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ふにんき' read in word?",
        "answer": "не популярний"
    },
    {
        "id": "25",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんこうえん' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий парк"
    },
    {
        "id": "26",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぎんこうか' read in word?",
        "answer": "банкір"
    },
    {
        "id": "27",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さっか' read in word?",
        "answer": "письменник"
    },
    {
        "id": "28",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんさくぶん' read in word?",
        "answer": "новий твір"
    },
    {
        "id": "29",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ところ' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце"
    },
    {
        "id": "30",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せまくて, ちいさいところ' read in word?",
        "answer": "Вузькі, малі місця"
    },
    {
        "id": "31",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'じゅうしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "адреса"
    },
    {
        "id": "32",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'きんじょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "околиця"
    },
    {
        "id": "33",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'めいじょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "визначні місця"
    },
    {
        "id": "34",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とくべつなしごとすること' read in word?",
        "answer": "роблять особливу роботу"
    },
    {
        "id": "35",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けんきゅうじょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "лабораторія"
    },
    {
        "id": "36",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しやくしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "посольство"
    },
    {
        "id": "37",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'けいむしょ' read in word?",
        "answer": "в’язниця"
    },
    {
        "id": "38",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ジョウ・ば' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце"
    },
    {
        "id": "39",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ひとがあつまるところです' read in word?",
        "answer": "місце, де збираються люди"
    },
    {
        "id": "40",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'かいじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "зал засідань"
    },
    {
        "id": "41",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'よくじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "баня, душ"
    },
    {
        "id": "42",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'いちば' read in word?",
        "answer": "ринок, базар"
    },
    {
        "id": "43",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'なにかおこなうことです' read in word?",
        "answer": "щось трапляється(івенти, події)"
    },
    {
        "id": "44",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'げきじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "театр"
    },
    {
        "id": "45",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しきじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "зал церемонії"
    },
    {
        "id": "46",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'せんじょう' read in word?",
        "answer": "фронт, поле бою"
    },
    {
        "id": "47",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'く' read in word?",
        "answer": "сторожити"
    },
    {
        "id": "48",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とちをわけたところ' read in word?",
        "answer": "земельні ділянки поділені"
    },
    {
        "id": "49",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'がっく' read in word?",
        "answer": "шкільний район"
    },
    {
        "id": "50",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'とっく' read in word?",
        "answer": "спеціальна зона"
    },
    {
        "id": "51",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しんじゅくく' read in word?",
        "answer": "район Шінджюку"
    },
    {
        "id": "52",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'チ・ジ' read in word?",
        "answer": "земля"
    },
    {
        "id": "53",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ちめんやとち' read in word?",
        "answer": "земельні ділянки і поверхня землі"
    },
    {
        "id": "54",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'しゃくち' read in word?",
        "answer": "оренда землі"
    },
    {
        "id": "55",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'ぼち' read in word?",
        "answer": "цвинтар"
    },
    {
        "id": "56",
        "question": "How is the hiragana 'さんち' read in word?",
        "answer": "скеляста місцина"
    }
]